chooseyourdiet.com 2016-03-06

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Last Revised: February 1, 2006

**An Overview**   
ChooseYourDiet.com provides information and services relating to weight loss.  The website is currently located at [http://www.chooseyourdiet.com](http://www.chooseyourdiet.com/) and e-mail newsletters are also offered (collectively known as the “Site”).  ChooseYourDiet.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information, and providing a safe and secure environment for our users. 

**The purpose of this ChooseYourDiet.com privacy policy (the "Policy") is to help you understand what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit the Site, how we may use that information, whether we will disclose it, and how you can correct the information. Please note that by using the Site, you signify your agreement with this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Site. Your continued use of the Site after any changes to the Policy will mean that you have accepted the changes; therefore please bookmark this page and review it frequently. If we decide to change the Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it.**

Please note that the Policy applies only to the Site, and not to other websites to which we link, or to advertisers on the Site. Your use of the Site is governed by ChooseYourDiet.com's [Terms of Service](http://www.chooseyourdiet.com/pages/Terms-of-Service) and by other published rules pertaining to particular products and services offered throughout the Site. 

**Children's Information**   
The Site is not directed toward children under thirteen years of age. ChooseYourDiet.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age. **If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information through the Site.**

**The Information We Gather**   
ChooseYourDiet.com collects information from you at several different points on the Site in the manner set forth below. Whenever we collect personal information, we will make an effort to include a link to the Policy on that page. 

**Free Diet Assessment**   
In order to use certain services on the Site, a user must provide a limited amount of personal information.  This includes, but is not limited to, your height, weight, e-mail address, desired weight goals and gender. 

**Send-To-A-Friend**   
If you elect to use the "Send-To-A-Friend" service on the Site, we will ask for your friend's name(s) and e-mail address(es). ChooseYourDiet.com will automatically send a one-time e-mail inviting your friend(s) to visit the Site. We will store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. 

**E-Mail Newsletters**   
If you would like to subscribe to one or more of ChooseYourDiet.com’s newsletters, please visit [http://www.chooseyourdiet.com](http://www.chooseyourdiet.com/) .  If you would like to unsubscribe to any of our newsletters or choose not to receive special offers from ChooseYourDiet.com or our partners, please refer to the instructions in the newsletters or special offer e-mails that you are receiving from us.  Alternatively, you can send us mail at:  ChooseYourDiet c/o Flatiron Media, 20 West 22nd Street, Suite 908, New York, NY 10010.  

**User Reviews**  
We provide a service that allows users to add their own reviews to our content.  Please note that the reviews or any other information you provide that is placed on the Site will be available for any user to read, and is therefore no longer private.  ChooseYourDiet.com owns the rights to this content and reserves the right to publish such reviews in other media formats, in its sole discretion. 

**How We Use The Information That We Gather**   
ChooseYourDiet.com uses information obtained from users as stated in this Policy.  ChooseYourDiet.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to ChooseYourDiet.com’s partners who work on behalf of or with ChooseYourDiet.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help ChooseYourDiet.com or its partners to communicate with you about offers from ChooseYourDiet.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information with other parties; 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ChooseYourDiet.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

To manage how ChooseYourDiet.com can communicate with you, please visit [http://www.chooseyourdiet.com](http://www.chooseyourdiet.com/).

**Disclosure of Personal Information in the Event of Merger or** **Sale** **of Assets**   
ChooseYourDiet.com, or its related entites, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or all or substantially all of their respective assets could be acquired. Should such a combination, acquisition or transaction occur, you should expect that ChooseYourDiet.com would share some or all of your personal information with the acquiring or merged entity to continue serving you and other users of the Site. 

**Cobranded and Other Affiliated Sites**   
Certain information or services offered or provided on or through the Site from time to time may be provided on or through other sites operated by or in conjunction with third party providers (“Partners”). These sites may have the same “look and feel” of the Site, and are often cobranded, such that a Partner’s logo or name may appear on the site, or the Partner’s name may appear in the URL. Aggregate or personally identifiable information collected about you on these sites may be shared by ChooseYourDiet.com with that Partner. A Partner will not rent, sell, or disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless you consent to its doing so, for example, by opting-in while on a particular site to receive information or offers from a Partner’s affiliates, partners, or other third parties. 

**Third Party Links and Member Websites**   
You acknowledge that we do not monitor, control or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any third parties, any co-branded or other affiliated sites which may or may not be owned or operated by or in conjunction with ChooseYourDiet.com, or any credit card order processors, product shippers or other third parties who provide services throughout the Site. Accordingly, ChooseYourDiet.com assumes no liability or responsibility for the information collection and privacy practices of any third party. In addition, ChooseYourDiet.com is not responsible for the content of any third party websites, including a third party's use of any cookies or any other information (such as IP address, browser type or operating system) collected when you "click-through" links to their sites or view advertisements served by them. Even though certain information collected by such third parties might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with their privacy practices, and to contact such third parties if you have any questions about their respective privacy policies. 

In addition, the Site may provide links to other Internet websites or resources ("Linked Sites"). ChooseYourDiet.com neither controls nor endorses such Linked Sites nor have we reviewed or approved any content that appears on such Linked Sites. You acknowledge and agree that ChooseYourDiet.com is not responsible for the legality, accuracy or inappropriate nature of any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such Linked Sites. You further acknowledge and agree that ChooseYourDiet.com shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods, and services available on or through any such Linked Site. 

**Security**   
The Site uses reasonable security methods to protect the data that resides on our servers. However, no security system is impenetrable. ChooseYourDiet.com cannot warrant or guarantee the security of its servers, nor can it guarantee that information that users supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to ChooseYourDiet.com over the Internet. If we ever ask users to enter credit card numbers, that information shall always be encrypted. 

**How To Contact Us**   
Should you have any questions or concerns about the Policy, please send an e-mail to [privacy@chooseyourdiet.com](mailto:privacy@chooseyourdiet.com).
